<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sous Chefs</title>
    <link>http://sous-chefs.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sous Chefs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 20:24:17 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://sous-chefs.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>board nominations</title>
      <link>http://sous-chefs.org/posts/board-nominations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 20:24:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sous-chefs.org/posts/board-nominations/</guid>
      <description>Vote We&amp;rsquo;ve reached the time of year to vote in another set of board members.
What we&amp;rsquo;re looking for This year we&amp;rsquo;re pushing for a more diverse crowd of maintainers and advocates. If you can help fill this stop please apply!
What&amp;rsquo;s in it for me? Fame, glory, riches.
Are not included, but you will get to shape the direction of Sous-Chefs. Read membership for more information about what the board does.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://sous-chefs.org/becoming-a-member/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sous-chefs.org/becoming-a-member/</guid>
      <description>Becoming a Member Join us on the Chef community slack, say hi then;
Send a PR to https://github.com/sous-chefs/terraform-github-org
Add yourself to: members.tf chef_de_partie.tf
If there is a cookbook you wish to become a maintainer of then add yourself to that repo&amp;rsquo;s corresponding file e.g. for sc-mongodb, add yourself to mongodb.tf (of course after discussing it in slack)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://sous-chefs.org/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sous-chefs.org/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Code of Conduct Sous Chefs are dedicated to providing a harassment-free cookbook experience for everyone, regardless of gender, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, or religion. We do not tolerate harassment of Sous Chefs participants in any form.
All communication should be appropriate for a professional audience including people of many different backgrounds.
Be kind to others. Do not insult or put down other community members. Behave professionally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://sous-chefs.org/contributing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sous-chefs.org/contributing/</guid>
      <description>Contributing to Sous-Chefs We are glad you want to contribute to a sous-chefs cookbook! The first step is the desire to improve the project.
Quick-contribute  Create an issue on the GitHub issue tracker (see issues_url in the cookbook&amp;rsquo;s metadata.rb) Link to your patch as a rebased git branch or pull request from the ticket  We regularly review contributions and will get back to you if we have any suggestions or concerns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://sous-chefs.org/departure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sous-chefs.org/departure/</guid>
      <description>Leaving Sous Chefs If a maintainer wants to stop or leave, it&amp;rsquo;s cool. We&amp;rsquo;ll gladly point to the project&amp;rsquo;s new home and keep an archive of the old history.
When the cookbook is for end-of-life tech If a cookbook is for software that&amp;rsquo;s no longer feasible to keep running, like old open source, old commercial stuff, anything that can&amp;rsquo;t be downloaded; then we update the cookbook README.md to mark as deprecated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://sous-chefs.org/licenses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sous-chefs.org/licenses/</guid>
      <description>Licenses Table of Contents  Software License
 Apache License LICENSE file Apache License Header Apache License in the README  Documentation License
 Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International LICENSE File Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International Icon   Software License The preferred software license to publish the work of Sous Chefs is Apache License. All published work must be under an Open Source Software license.
You can see the different licenses available here: http://choosealicense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://sous-chefs.org/membership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sous-chefs.org/membership/</guid>
      <description>Members Who we are
Board The board is responsible for those things that are not easily distributed.
 enforce the code of conduct enforce licenses manage finances control access to community services  This list should remain as small as possible. If it is possible to automate, it should be automated.
The board reserves the authority to do any lawful act necessary to operate the community, but we&amp;rsquo;ll try to avoid wielding this hammer as much as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://sous-chefs.org/repository-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sous-chefs.org/repository-setup/</guid>
      <description> Repository Layout  Master is always protected. Review where possible must have a second pair of eyes. Squash merging is up to the repository primary maintainer
 We aim to have clean understandable updates, and good git history. Rather than hiding a mess under the carpet.   Example </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://sous-chefs.org/transferring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sous-chefs.org/transferring/</guid>
      <description>Transferring a Cookbook to the Sous Chefs Got a cookbook you&amp;rsquo;d like help with? We&amp;rsquo;d love to help!
Before you begin We need to work with the GitHub repo owner and supermarket cookbook owner. If you aren&amp;rsquo;t this person, let us know and we&amp;rsquo;ll try to contact them. If necessary, fine beverages and chocolate chip cookies may be provided to encourage them to work with us.
When this is not possible please see forking</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>